Is there anything you're still unsure about?
Who knows if any
of this is real.
Maybe you hired all these
people to act for you.
Idiot!
I once saw a mysterious crystal star
a ring in Persia.
Its radiance is unmistakable.
I swear on my name. This ring is the genuine article!
Lord Severin, the lords from
every region of Golantis have arrived.
They await your command outside.
Let them in.
By Lord Severin's command, let them through!
What?
Heads of state from other kingdoms?
Could he actually be the Godfather?
Make way!
Godfather!
Congratulations on your wedding, my lord!
The King has arrived!
- Your Majesty!
Today is the Godfather’s wedding day.
Everyone rise.
Godfather.
Congratulations on your wedding, my lord.
No need for formalities.Take your seat.
I have some private
matters to settle first.
On such a joyous day,
what private matter requires your attention?
Many people here think I’m
an impostor and want me executed.
You are the nominal
ruler of this continent.
Bear witness.
What?!
Lord Severin may
keep a low profile,
but he has saved Golantis
from disaster time and again.
Who dares question the Godfather’s identity?